DrJill: Hello and welcome to Let's Learn English with Anna.
DrJill: I am Dr.
DrJill: Jill.
DrJill: But who are you?
DrJill: Today we answer that question.
DrJill: Who are you?
DrJill: So let's go to Anna's treehouse.
DrJill: She helps us answer the question, who are you?
Anna: Hi!
Anna: Welcome to my treehouse!
Anna: I am Anna.
Max: And I am Max.
Anna: That is Max.
Anna: Max is an E mailbox.
Max: Anna, I have our question for today.
Anna: Thanks, Max.
Anna: Who are you?
Anna: I and
Anna: I am Its
Anna: I'm not done yet.
Max: Oh, Gory.
Anna: Max, I'm done now.
Max: And I am Max.
DrJill: Nice song.
DrJill: Okay friends, say the question after me.
DrJill: Who are you?
DrJill: Now let's meet some new friends.
DrJill: They answered today's question too.
Alexa: I am Zalitsi.
Alexa: I am Anna Abidi.
Alexa: Hi, I am Alexa.
DrJill: How many friends do you see?
DrJill: One, two, three.
DrJill: That's right, three friends.
DrJill: Okay, now let's play a game with our friends.
DrJill: They say their names.
DrJill: You listen.
DrJill: Are you ready?
DrJill: Here they are.
DrJill: Find the names with the letter A.
DrJill: I am Zanet Si.
Alexa: I am Anna Abhiri
Alexa: Hi, I am Alexa.
DrJill: That's right.
DrJill: Alexa and Anna have the letter A.
DrJill: Good job!
DrJill: Now let's go back to Anna's treehouse.
DrJill: She talks about other words with the letter A.
DrJill: Let's go!
DrJill: Who are you?
Anna: Who are you?
Anna: I am Anna.
Anna: Anna starts with an A.
Anna: But the letter A has many sounds.
Anna: A
Anna: Ah, apple.
Anna: Ah, Anna.
Anna: Anna ate an apple.
Anna: Who are you?
Max: I am Max.
Max: You are Anna.
Anna: Who are you?
Anna: Who am I?
Anna: I need to walk.
Anna: Who?
Anna: Who
Anna: Who are you?
Anna: You are an owl.
Anna: One owl.
Anna: Two owls.
Anna: Three owls.
Anna: I love owls.
Anna: Three owls!
Anna: And I love to walk.
Max: Anna, it's time to go.
Anna: Thanks, Max.
DrJill: Come back again though.
DrJill: Goodbye
DrJill: Now you try it.
DrJill: Ask your family and friends, who are you?
Alexa: How do they answer?
Alexa: I am Zalitsu.
Alexa: I am Anna Abidi.
Alexa: Hi, I am Alexa.
DrJill: See you next time on Let's Learn English with Anna.
Anna: I am honor, I am honor, I am honor, I am on